you opened your mouth about teachers in Georgia I
ты ты открыл рот про учителей в Грузии Я
told you nothing, look, you
тебе нагу лил давай смотри это ты до
opened your mouth before Let me
этого открывал рот Давай я тебе
compare your poor Russia with the French,
французами сравнивал твою нищую Россию
you told me Georgia Let’s compare a
ты мне сказал Грузия Давай по сравним
teacher in Volgograd 280 dollars
учительница в Волгограде 280 долларов
28,000 rubles a
28.000 руб
beggar and our Georgian teacher 550
нищая и наша грузинская учительница 550
dollars in  twice
долларов в два раза
as much Good evening Where are you from
больше Вечер добрый Вы откуда
Volgograd Russia I'm from Georgia
Волгоград Россия Я из Грузии
Kutaisi What's your name Oh well I'm
Кутаиси Вас как зовут А а ну я
good that you want to hear what your
хорошо что вы хотите услышать как вас
name is Sergey Sergey me Irakli I want to
зовут Сергей Сергей меня Ираклий хочу
ask Sergey How are you doing in
спросить Сергей Как вам поживает в
Russia in
России в
Volgograd
Волгограде
good how good Well should I personally
хорошо насколько хорошо Ну мне лично
complain at all  nothing
жаловаться вообще не на что
Cool Well,
Прикольно Ну вот
look at what a person could do
смотрите на что може ж дался человек
when
когда
Well, even here I am a village person from a
Ну даже вот я поселковый человек с
village. In our village there are roads
посёлка У нас вот в посёлке дороги
asphalt,
асфальт
village lighting, work, everything is there. There are
посёлок освещение работа всё есть
a lot of stores, but they put on different types of meat. Well,
Магазинов много мясные одела разные Ну
what can I complain about? It’s cool. That
на что я могу жаловаться прикольно То
is, in principle  civilization has already
есть в принципе цивилизация уже в ваш
reached your village, asphalt has been laid, light
поселок дошла асфальт проложили свет
has been laid
провели
Yes, in general, I’m saying Well, it’s been a long time
Да в общем говорю Ну давно
Listen,
уже Слушайте а
why? For example, people in French
почему Например люди во французских
villages, they also have asphalt light,
посёлках у них тоже есть асфальт свет
sometimes they are dissatisfied with something. Why is
иногда бывают что-то недовольно Почему
that And you know
так А знаете почему
why, look at the human fax,
почему смотрите человеческий фак
it’s always not enough
сю всегда мало
Yes  look, you go to the store
Да вот смотрите Вы заходите в магазин
correctly, there is meat, there is bread, there
правильно Мясо есть Так Хлеб есть Так
is cottage cheese, there is milk, yes, it’s
творог есть молоко есть
not enough for you, yes, because I’m a human being, and
Да Вам мало Да потому что я человек а
you have
вам
enough for
достаточно для
food, no, for
питания нет для
still life, for nutrition, that’s all, but for life,
натюрморта для питания всё а для жизни
for
для
life, you create a situation for yourself, that
жизни ты сам себе создаёшь ситуацию то
is, look.  I live
есть вот смотрите Я живу
Yes, this is how much I earned
Да у меня вот столько-то я зарабатывал
I don’t have enough And how much did you
мне мало не хвата А сколько вы
earn
зарабатывали
for I earn I’m a shift worker I
за Я зарабатываю я вахтовик Я
earn 200,000 a month on a shift in the
зарабатываю 200.000 в месяц на вахте на
north yes 2,000
севере да 2.000
to
до
no from Moscow and throughout the country I travel I’m a
нет от Москвы и по всей стране езди я
high-altitude
высотник
installer but you know what  I noticed Yeah,
монтажник но знаете что я заметил Угу
when you earn
когда зарабатываешь
70,000 it’s not enough when you earn 200,000, it’s
70.000 мало когда зарабатываешь 200.000
also
тоже
a little cool, the human factor, the
мало прикольно человеческий фактор
human factor, how much I don’t
фактор человеческий сколько не
earn a little, the question is why do people in
зарабатываю мало вопрос почему люди во
France, Germany, and
Франции в Германии
America go to some kind of rallies?
в Америке выходят на какие-то митинги
Because something is not enough for them, and the Russians don’t
Потому что им что-то мало а россияне не
go to
выходят на
rallies, but  because Russians understand
митинги а потому что россияне понимают
one
одну
thing, look in France There, yes, they go
вещь смотрите во Франции Там да выходят
to rallies, little, little, it changes, it does
на митинги мало мало что это меняет
n’t change anything. Russia, I don’t understand what
ничего не меняет Россия не понимаю то
you went to the rally, what will it change? Yes, it won’t change anything. It
что ну вышел ты На митинг что это
will change the Constitution, no, it will
поменяет Конституцию поменяет нет
change politics, too,
политику поменяет тоже
no, that is, they will
нет то есть
go out.  This has been going on for decades and
выходят Вот это десятилетиями выходит и
nothing has changed for them. And what is
ничего не меняется у них нет А что у них
changing for them? Well, for example, in 1968, they
меняется Ну например в 1968 году они
changed the Constitution well, there
Конституцию там хорошо поменяли там
were student clashes with the police, and they became super rich
вообще были и что они супер богатые
in comparison with the Russians. Yes, they are
стали в сравнении с россиянами Да они
super rich. Well, that’s yours.  I don’t
супер богатые Ну это ваше мнение наве не
know this opinion because my opinion is that
зна такое потому что мо мнение то что
No, they are not bots richer than
Нет они не боты богаче
the Russians What kind of car do you have? Do
россиян Какая у вас
you know how to use cars? For
машина мне А вы по машинам умеете для
example, for an example I usually have a
примера У меня обычно
Lagran Well, like every
лагран Ну как у каждого
Frenchman, but what’s good? For me they
француза а то что хорошо Это по мне
compared  My friends have both Toyota and
сравнили А у меня у друзей и Тойота и
other Mashas. Let's not just
другие Маши Давайте вот не просто
some guy
какой-то
get 200,000 a month, you understand
там 200.000 получает в месяц понимаете
this in general Wow, and you think I have money and
это вообще Вау а вы думаете мне деньги а
I think I should have money somewhere,
мне деньги думаете деньги никуда девать
or what? Where do you put it?
что ли А куда вы их
Where am I doing? I have a question  first
девает куда я делаю У меня во-первых
there is a beloved girl
есть любимая девушка
so please she wanted an iPhone
так пожалуйста она захотела себе iPhone
I bought an iPhone I wanted a tablet for my child I
Купил iPhone захотела ребёнку планшет
bought a tablet I wanted to go here here
купил планшет захотела сходить туда сюда
here ok let’s
сюда хорошо
go so It’s all money
сходим так Это всё деньги
Yeah Or maybe a girl look at you
Угу А может девушка смотрите у вас
look at you have a girl let’s say the wife is a
смотрите у вас девушка допустим жена
girl and she has such needs buy
девушка да у неё потребности такие купи
me a lollipop  -chups everything to me, for example
мне чупа-чупс мне всё к примеру
Yeah And I have another girl b Well,
Ага А у меня вот другая девушка б Ну я
what am I And I understand correctly what kind of
что А я правильно понимаю а какой у неё
iPhone she has what kind of iPhone did you buy her
iPhone какой вы купили ей
iPhone fourteenth iPhone
iPhone четырнадцатый iPhone
fourteenth iPhone I understand correctly
четырнадцатый iPhone я правильно понимаю
that she is getting into your Lada with this fourteenth iPhone
что она с этим четырнадцатым Айфоном
yes A  It’s all funny the car is a car, what’s
да А всё прикол машина есть машина в чём
the problem so the phone has a
проблема так телефон есть
phone and why should I
телефон а что я должен на Росс ройсе
drive a Ross Royce like this on a Ross Royce Yes, I just
ездить такой на рос ройсе Да не я просто
don’t understand why she really needed
не понимаю зачем вот ей прям нужен был
this fourteenth iPhone in short Yes, but
короче этот четырнадцатый iPhone Да но
at the same time she drives a
при этом она ездит на
Lada Well then  I understand you, but it
Ладе Ну тогда вас понимаю я а мне
seems to me that the girl who wants the
кажется что девушка которая хочет
fourteenth iPhone clearly doesn’t
четырнадцатый iPhone явно не на Ладе
want to
хочет
ride in a Lada. But this is where you’re wrong.
прокатиться А вот в этом вы ошибаетесь А
Well, you know why? Because the
ну а знаете знаете почему Потому
girls are all girls. Many people want an
что у девушек у все девушки Многие хотят
iPhone there. Although everyone has a good dress,
себе там iPhone Хотя всех хорошее платье
yes. Which one?  to drive a car Yes, they
да А на какой машине ездить Да это они
understand that
понимают то что
everyone’s needs and perceptions are a little
потребность и восприятие у всех немного
bit different. I don’t understand, let’s say you’re semi. Let’s say
чуть разное не понял допустим вы полу
you get, for example, a
Вот вы допустим получаете к примеру
million a month, yes Yeah, and I get 200,000 a
миллион В месяц да Угу А я 200000 В
month, yes. So you can afford a
месяц да Так вы можете позволить себе
good car and an iPhone, yes that’s right.
хорошую машину и iPhone да правильно Так
and let’s say, well, I can’t
а я вот допустим Ну я не могу себе
afford a car like this, but in general,
позволить машину такую но в целом
for the same money I can
за те же самые деньги я могу позволить
at least afford to please my girlfriend with
хотя бы порадовать свою девушку
an iPhone, I understand. And you’re at home now, or maybe I
Айфоном понял А это вы сейчас дома илий
have a car, even if
машина у меня пускай пускай машина у
my car is not the best, not by itself but  I
меня не самая хорошая не само но я
’m trying to please someone
пытаюсь радовать кого Девушку
My girlfriend And where are you now?
свою А вы сейчас где находитесь
At home in the village with my mother I understand
дома в деревне у матери у матери понял А
why with my mother in the village and not with
почему у матери в деревне а не с
my girlfriend because I’m my homeland I
своей потому что я это моя родина Я
came to
приехал
rest in the sense of coming to rest and
отдохнуть в смысле отдохнуть приехал а
you can’t relax with your child  with
вы не можете отдохнуть с ребёнком с
a girl, I don’t have a child, I have a
девушкой у меня нету ребёнка у меня есть
girlfriend, so you told the girl
девушка так у девушки же вы говорили
the child that she wants to buy him a tablet, she
ребёнок что она планшет ему хочет купить
has a child. I don’t understand,
у неё есть ребёнок У меня нет понял то
you live with her
вы живёте с ней
together, yes, and now where is
вместе да так А сейчас где же
she? She’s in the apartment, and why are you  You’re not with her, you’re
она она в квартире а почему ты не с ней
not supporting her morally, you’re not keeping
не поддерживаешь её морально не греешь
her warm, that’s also an interesting question.
её вот тут тоже тоже интересный вопрос А
Why can’t I relax
я что не могу отдохнуть
separately with
отдельно с
my mother, why with my mother and friends I have
мамой почему с мамой с друзьями у меня
friends from the village and you came to get drunk
друзья поселковые ребяты а ты побухать
Well, it turns out that’s all Yesterday
приехал Ну получается да всё Вчера у
I had one of those too  he’s basically
меня один такой тоже был он там короче
a multimillionaire, like that’s all, but he’s
мультимиллионер типа всё но в сарае
drinking in his grandmother’s barn. Yes, he
бухает у бабушки Да
was. No, what does it matter? I’m not a multi-millionaire. I
был Не ну причём муль я не мульти я тебе
told you that I
что сказал то что миллион
earn a million. The question is why the French, with
зарабатываю вопрос почему французам с
their salaries, can
ихними зарплатами они могут себе
afford both an iPhone and a
позволить и iPhone и
car. And why can the Georgians afford a
машину А почему грузины могут позволить
prize in  Russia, head of
приз в Россию зава
France, we are talking to you now Yes, you
Францию говорим сейчас с тобой Да ты
say that in France people are not
говоришь что во Франции люди не
richer and a car
богаче и машину
and an iPhone, yes, yes, maybe a leg What Well,
и iPhone да да ножку может Какая Ну
let's go to Khatam potse, the old Russian
давай по Хатам поце старая русская
mantra rent Well look, let's The
мантра квартплата Хорошо смотри давай
Frenchman earns 6,000 euros per month
Француз зарабатывает в месяц 6.000 евро
and his rent is 30 euros This  In
да квартплата у него 30 евро Это При
what kind of work does He earn 6,000
какой работе Он зарабатывает 6.000
teacher teacher
учитель учитель
yes I don’t earn 6,000 euros in France
да не зарабатываю 6.000 евро во Франции
And
А
how much 3,000 euros
сколько 3.000 евро
I’ll believe No not six six no even if
поверю Нет не шесть шесть нет даже если
3 but 30 euros the rent remains
3 но 30 евро квартплата остаётся
2700 plus
2700 плюс
the rent
квартплата
food
питание
clothes and
одежда и
Georgians what are you cutting off let’s go with the
грузины что ты срезается давай с
French Ponya Here they are holding a rally  Don’t
французами Поня Вот они митингуют Да не
wait, why are you moving out so
подожди А что ты съезжаешь так
soon? I don’t know, by the way,
сразу Я не знаю у нас кстати очень много
we have a lot of Russians who have been here for 2 years already
русских уже 2 года приехали нам у нас
working here. Here I was in a cafe and there was a
тут работают Вот у меня Я в кафе был да
Russian waitress who came to work
официантка русская приехали на заработки
since the second year, we have a lot of people in
с д второго года у нас очень много в
Tbilis  Russians have come here and they say
тбилис русских по приезжала говорят
life has become difficult because of the sanctions. But
тяжело жить стало из-за санкций А у нас
here in Russia, Georgians haven’t seen anything like this.
а у нас в России грузин не видел такого
Here we have Russian beggars who
вот у нас попрошайки российские
come and work for us,
приезжают типа и работают у нас
sweeping there, that’s strange, here it’s
подметают туда вот это странно
Russian Sergei, in short, he’s
у нас этон русский Сергей короче он у
sweeping here  in the yard, by the way, Seryoga is
нас тут подметает во дворе кстати Серёга
also good like you, by the way,
такой тоже хороший как тебя кстати
Seryoga, and you know, don’t tell fairy tales. Do you
Серёга а а ты знаешь сказки не
know why? Because the
рассказывай Знаешь почему Потому что э
sanctions didn’t affect Russia at all,
санкции на Россию вообще не повлияли
yes, yes, yes,
никак да Ну да да
seriously, seriously, yes, that is, your prices have not
Серьёзно Серьёзно да то есть у вас не
increased
поднялись
by 10 rubles
цены на 10 руб
so and so  It’s just you,
такой-то просто это ты бы сколько у вас
how much do you have, how much does your teacher
сколько у вас учительница
earn in salary? I don’t know, I don’t communicate. 17,000 rubles is much more than you think, how much now, what is your village called, I’ll now google the
называется я сейчас загуглю зарплату
teacher’s salary, more than 40,000,
учителя больше 40.000
they received 400 dollars.
получали 400 долларов
I said more, but didn’t specify how much.  and
Я сказа больше но не уточнил сколько и
more than 400 dollars, so look at the average
больше 400 долларов так смотри средняя
salary of a teacher in Volgograd in 2024
зарплата учителя в Волгограде 2024 год
27.24 rubles in short 28,000 here is the official
27.24 рубля короче 28.000 вот официаль
gorodrabot ru website for all vacancies the
городработ ру сайт по всем вакансиям
average salary of a teacher in Volgograd
средняя зарплата учителя в Волгограде
is the average it’s not even the minimum
это средняя это даже не минимальная
28,000 rubles What 40 are you telling me
28.000 руб Какие 40 ты мне рассказываешь
and in Georgia 3
и в Грузии 3
Gri So look  you tell me 400
Гри Так посмотри ты расска 400
40 in Georgia how much Tell me Let me tell you
40 в Грузии сколько Скажи мне Дава скажу
in Georgia
в Грузии
Come on Let me go now too I’ll
Давай А давай сейчас тоже пойду забью
forget and ask
поинтересуюсь
so And by the way listen dude and
так А ты кстати слушай чувачок а ты
when do you know what you are doing You when you
когда этот знаешь что делаешь Ты когда
compare prices Well salary and
цены сравниваешь Ну зарплату и
food uh clothes Georgian three uh
сва питание э одежда грузинский три ээ
average salary  school teachers in
средняя зарплата школьных учителей в
Georgia are about 577 dollars this is in the twenty-
Грузии около 577 долларов это в двадцать
second year o In short, you’ve already lost everything
втором году о Короче всё Ты уже проиграл
in
по
G yes And food food housing accommodation
Г да А питание питание жильё проживание
550 dollars with us Look, in short, uh, a
550 долларов у нас Смотри короче ээ
teacher in Georgia receives
учитель в Грузии получает в долларах в
twice as much in dollars as a teacher in Volgograd,
два раза больше чем учитель в Волгограде
everything about  Now Let's see Don't
всё прои по Сейчас Сейчас посмотрим Не
worry, your teacher earns
переживай у вас получает учительница 280
$280 on average in Volgograd,
долларов в среднем в Волгограде вообще
by the way, you know honestly And at least you're Georgian Well,
кстати знаешь честно А ты хоть грузин Ну
I never understood one thing And what does it have to do with
я никогда не понимал одного А причём
comparing compare prices between
здесь сравнивает сравнивают цены между
countries, look, he opened his mouth about teachers
странами смотри открыл рот про учителей
in Georgia I'm nagulino for you
в Грузии Я тебе нагулино
[music]
[музыка]
I compared your poor
я тебе французами сравнивал твою нищую
Russia with the French, you told me Georgia Let’s
Россию ты мне сказал Грузия Давай по
compare a teacher in Volgograd 280
сравним учительница в Волгограде 280
dollars 28,000 rubles
долларов 28.000 руб
a beggar and our Georgian teacher 550
нищая и наша грузинская учительница 550
dollars is twice as much as a Georgian
долларов в два раза больше грузины
Georgians in Russia are like if you come
грузины в России как если вы приезжаете
to us to work in our restaurants all
к нам работать у нас в ресторанах вся
the service is now
обслуга сейчас
Russian Yeah,
Российская Ага
all Georgians are in
все грузины в
Russia Come on, look for it, look for belashko
России Давай давай ищи ищи белашко
salaries,
зарплат
come on, you
давай дава У вас же даже в холодильнике
don’t even have food in the refrigerator normally, the
еды нету нормально у
Russians of course don’t have meat, there’s nothing, no
русских конечно мяса нету ничего не нету
matter what Show me in the refrigerator
по-любому Покажи вот в холодильнике У
What kind of food do you have, there’s no meat, listen,
тебя что за продукты нету мяса по слуша
tell me  who tells you about meat
вот скажи вот кто тебе рассказывает мяса
and dairy, not my friends who live in
и молочки не у меня знакомые живут в
Russia, have already come to see me in Georgia, ate
России уже приезжали ко мне в Грузию ели
here for a whole month, from
тут целый месяц отъ
food with 58 dollars of
едалия с 58 долларов
accommodation. Let's say this is the teacher's salary, what are
проживания Давай это зарплату учителя
you
что ты там
starting there, not me, accommodation while I'm looking at
начинаешь не я проживание пока смотрю
Let's look at the salaries first, look at
Давай сначала зарплаты посмотри
the salary, accommodation, wife's salary  And so
зарплату проживание жне зарплата И так
on, let's look. Show realistically that
дальше давай смотри Покажи реально что у
you have food in the refrigerator, that you
тебя есть продукты в холодильнике что ты
won't be in trouble eating, you don't have any
не беду ешь походу у тебя нету нету
Russians, because of the stations,
русских у вас из-за станций ни молока
now you have no milk, no
теперь нету Ни
bread. Judging by my muscles, I'm not in trouble,
хлеба Судя Судя по моим мышцам я не беду
and judging by yours  Judging by your mice
и а Судя по твоему Судя по твоим мыш
muscles, you don’t have
мышц нету у
swelling of the
тебя это опухлости
bodies dadada Well, show me show me the
тел дадада Ну покажи покажи покажи
trapezoid Yes yes
трапецию Да да
yes the trapezoid If you had food you
да трапец Если у тебя были продукты ты
would show it from the refrigerator Look, the
бы показал с холодильника Вот смотри
milk is fresh But there’s nothing
молочка есть свежая А так нету ничего
You know what makes me happy You know what makes me
Знаешь что меня радует знаешь что меня
happy What after  Ukraine will have you Georgia
радует что после Украины вас Грузию
Russia will now And you are not afraid in the
Россия будет теперь А ты не боишься на
war
войне
Yeah, the Ukrainians also
Ага украинцы также
said Well, that’s how long it’s been in
говорили Ну вот сколько уже в
Ukraine and how many
Украине а скоко
hired Georgians and you will soon And why do you
наёмный грузин и ты скоро А почему ты
hate
так ненавидишь
Georgians so much And why do you hate Russians so much I
грузин А почему так ненавидишь русских Я
hate I just said that the French are
ненавижу Я просто сказал что французы
richer And you  somehow I started talking negatively about
богаче А ты как-то начал негативно О
Georgians, I showed you, I compared
грузинах я тебе показал сравнил
teachers' salaries with salaries, I showed you
зарплатой зарплаты учителей показал тебе
that a Georgian teacher is twice as
что грузинская учительница в два раза
rich and you got burned, you started talking negatively about
богаче и ты подгорел начал негативно о
Georgians, you started This type of thing, we
грузинах говорить ты начал Такой типа мы
Georgians live richly, but we're going to Russia,
грузины богато живём но в Россию едем
we don't live, but we live richer  than
мы нето живём но мы живём богаче чем
Russia
Россия
Yes, you are coming here, well, why are you coming
Да вы сюда едете ну зачем вы сюда едете
here, only crime bosses are coming here,
у нас едут только криминальные
they keep Russians, all
авторитеты они держат русских все
crime bosses in Russia are
криминальные авторитеты в России - это
Georgians, come on, let’s do it humanly,
грузины Давай давай по человеческие
without swearing, without anything Look,
хорошо без ругани без всего Смотри вот
let’s SD so that I can see your eyes and not
давай СД чтобы я твои глаза видел а не
your pimples  wait, if you don’t
твои прыщи стой если вам не нравится
like Russia, you don’t like Russia, well,
Россия вам не нравится Россия ну зачем
why, why are you coming here? Look, I’m sitting
ну зачем вы сюда едете Смотри я сижу у
in my city of Kutaisi, what are you
себя в городе Кутаиси что ты мне
presenting to me from your village like I’m
предъявляется из своего посёлка типа я
here, we have a teacher’s salary?
вот тут у нас зарплата учительницы Ты
Look, you’ve leaked, let’s look at 550
смотри что ты слился давай смотри 550
dollars  you average in Volgograd 280 is
долларов у вас среднее в Волгограде 280
half as much our teacher like
в два раза меньше наша учительница лайк
your
ваша
teacher yes And at the same time our
учительница да И при этом наша
teacher gives the minimum for food
учительница За продукты отдаёт минимум
for housing the minimum and wa Maxim our
за жильё минимум а ва Максиму наша
teacher with an iPhone and a car and
учительница с Айфоном и с машиной а у
without anything and I’m looking at your camera is
без ничего а я смотрю у тебя по камере
not ione  And
не ione А
look, I’m not a teacher, I haven’t
какая-то смотри я ж не учительница не
accumulated enough attention on
накопился на
your camera, I’m looking at the camera, it’s just
камеру у тебя смотрю камера просто
a bomb, the cell you
бомбическая та камера в которой ты
’re sitting in, you’re talking about a European one. Yes, why do
сидишь ты же про европейская Да а почему
you have such a negative attitude towards Europe?
ты так что так негативно к Европе
You’re talking about Asian
относишься ты про азиат
marriages, how are you serious? Why are you?  you
браки как ты серьёзно А почему ты
think I support same-sex people, I’m playing,
считаешь я поддерживаю однополые играю
you’re the one who has same-sex
вот ты как раз у тебя однополые
marriage, you live, you don’t live with a woman,
браки ты ты живёшь ты же не с женщиной
but with your friends, you came to
живёшь да а с дружками ты приехал чтобы
hang out with your friends on the crib here,
с дружками потусить на кроватке тут
but you didn’t, you left the girl and went
Да ты ж не ты уехал от девушки и поехал
there with the boys, yes  by
чтобы с пацанами там да по
Yes, this is not your Europe No, well, that’s how you have
Да это не ваша Европа Не ну так у вас
ROSI Look, let’s do this in Russia,
РОСИ Смотри вот давай так у вас в России
these are all Kirkorov Basques Well, come
вот эти все Киркоров Басков Ну давай
on, look, you can name at least
давай посмотри у вас можешь назвать хоть
one Georgian singer who
одного грузинского певца который
looks like a woman And I can name the Russian ones
выглядит как женщина А я могу российских
Kirkorov
назвать Киркоров
Basque this Blue  the moon is like Boris
Басков этот Голубая луна как Борис
Moisey They are all of these you have, this is your
моисее Они же все эти у вас это ваша
Russia something They are not Russian, it doesn’t even matter
Россия чтото Они не русские даже неважно
But this is your Russian stage, these are like
Но это ваша Российская эстрада э эти как
honored artists of
они заслуженные артисты
Russia, we don’t have that in Georgia Listen,
России у нас в Грузии такого нету Слушай
look at this Georgian by the way, what do you say, what do you
смотрите кстати е что ты скажешь что ты
say  why is it so common in Russia
скажешь почему у вас в России да
when men
распространено вот такое когда мужики
there Kirkorov in feathers performs somehow
там Киркоров в перьях выступает как-то
Yes, Boris Moisey in leopard skin is so
Да Борис моисее в леопардовой шкуре
ha-ha made up and the
такой там ха-ха накрашенный и поёт
blue
голубая
moon sings and why in Europe you are allowed
луна а почему у вас в Европе разрешена
to have sex marriages wait So this is yours  in
на полые браки подожди Так это у вас в
Russia we don’t have this in Georgia we
России такое у нас в Грузии нету у нас в
don’t have it in Georgia at all for Europe in Georgia
Грузии вообще нету за Европу в в Грузии
there is no same-sex marriage and in Georgia there is no and in
нету однополых браков и в Грузии нет и в
Georgia there are no such singers Like you and
Грузии нету таких певцов Как у вас а вы
you are Europeans Well
вы европейцы
you can explain, look Why
Ну вы Ты можешь объяснить смотри Почему
you have it on the central  on television, the main
у вас на центральном телевидении главный
singer of the country, Kirkorov, dresses in feathers
певец страны Киркоров надевается в перье
and women's outfits,
и в женские наряды
why and why are all the Georgians going to he
почему а почему все грузины едут
can’t answer because you have
на не может ответить потому что у вас
this one cavity on television,
вот эта одна полость на телевидении у
you have all these Putin For example, he
вас все вот эти Путин Например у него же
doesn’t have a wife, he’s with the laurel Truth or with
нету жены он с лавровым Правда или с
sandy not you don’t but that is, he
песковым не у тебя не а то есть он этот
turns out to be If he’s a man Yes he wants no
получается Если он мужчину Да хочет не
no Well it turns out He’s this one you just
не Ну получается Он этот ты только что
called Putin you admitted that the president of
назвал Путина ты признал что президент
your country is this
вашей страны этот
Okay or something Well why did you say that
О'кей что ли Ну почему ты же сказал что
he Well look come on Well  let's really
он Ну смотри давай Ну давай реально
look at Putin Putin is a man now Putin is a
смотри Путин Путин мужчина сечас Путин
man Who is his woman who is
мужчина Кто кто его женщина кто женщина
Putin's woman, unlike you, at least he
Путина в отличие от тебя у него хотя бы
had a wife who is Putin's woman now
жена была кто сейчас женщина Путина
how many does he not have a Georgian wife what
сколько у него нет жены
kind of wife does he have he
грузинка какая у него нет у него жены
doesn't have a Georgian wife no no see Georgians
грузинка нету нету видишь грузин Почему
Why  you are
у вас
the president And if you don’t have a wife, then right away
президент А если нет жены то сразу
who is
а кто
he? And you have a wife, it’s
он А у тебя есть жена
true that she’s Russian in circles. Well, don’t
есть правда её русский по кругу Да не же
look at
то смотри
Putin, you have Putin, let’s
Путин у тебя Путин давай
solve
реши
everything, it’s burnt, look, I’ll tell you what,
всё подгорел смотри я тебе вот что скажу
because you’re Russians, Yes, you live in poverty.
потому что вы русские Да живёте в бедни
We  We see how you live, yes,
Мы же видим как ты живёшь да у бабушки у
he came to see your mother at your grandmother’s, Yes, you
бабушки к маме он приехал Да ты
live, you live in poverty, and
живёшь ты живёшь в бедности и вместо
instead of thinking how to get out of
того чтобы думать как как вылезти из
this poverty without any enlightenment, you say,
этой нищеты без просвет най ты говоришь
Yes, you’re French there, you’re poor, you’re Georgians,
Да вы там французы там Бедные вы грузины
poor, and so on, Yes.  look at yourself,
бедный И так дальше Да посмотри на себя
you're a normal car - this is the limit of
ты ж нормальная машина - это предел
your dreams what's the sixteenth what's the
твоих мечтаний какой шестнадцатой какой
fourteenth iPhone dude say
четырнадцатый iPhone чувак говори
maximum it's a Nokia without a
максимум это Nokia без экрана типа
push-button screen I bought it girls and that's it, that's it,
кнопочную купил девушки и всё вот и всё
let's write on my Instagram I don't know
давай пиши на мий Instagram Я не знаю
what this is for, why what else?  there to
для чего це тоб для чого ще тоб там
marvel at the ocey mi face Ale for you
дивитись на оцей мий фейс Але для тебе
tse one two or three clicks
це один два або три клика
Ale you trimae me and I will be kazati Wow in
Але ты тримае мене и я буду казати Вау в
me there Kupa fouls and in me there will be a
мене там Купа фолов и в мене буде
classy mood to robiti new cool
класний настрий щоб робити новые крути
videos subscribe to my Ista popk Andriy
видео подпишись на мий Иста попк Андрий
like this let me
так давай я
estrus N
течка N